coworkingresources.org 2019-12-21

# Privacy Policy | Coworking Resources

Our Privacy Policy was last updated and posted on May 23, 2018. It governs the privacy terms of our Website, located at [http://www.coworkingresources.org ](http://www.coworkingresources.org/)and operated by Kisi Inc.

## Your Privacy

KISI Inc. follows all legal requirements to protect your privacy. Our Privacy Policy is a legal statement that explains how we may collect information from you, how we may share your information, and how you can limit our sharing of your information. You will see terms in our Privacy Policy that are capitalized. These terms have meanings as described in the Definitions section below.

## Definitions

“Non Personal Information” is information that is not personally identifiable to you and that we automatically collect when you access our Website with a web browser. It may also include publicly available information that is shared between you and others.“Personally Identifiable Information” is non-public information that is personally identifiable to you and obtained in order for us to provide you within our Website. Personally Identifiable Information may include information such as your name, email address, and other related information that you provide to us or that we obtain about you.

## Your Rights

For Personal Data that we process as a data controller, you may have the following rights in relation to your Personal Data, depending on applicable law:

### Right of access

If you ask us, we will confirm whether we are processing your Personal Data and, if so, provide you with a copy of that Personal Data (along with certain other details).

### Right to rectification

If your Personal Data is inaccurate or incomplete, you are entitled to ask that we correct or complete it.

### Right to erasure

You may ask us to delete or remove your Personal Account in some circumstances.

### Right to restrict processing

You may ask us to restrict or block the processing of your Personal Data in certain circumstances, such as where you contest the accuracy of that Personal Data or object to us processing it (but not continuing to store it). We will tell you before we lift any restriction on processing.

### Right to data portability

You may have the right to obtain the Personal Data we process about you in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format, and to reuse it elsewhere.

### Right to object

You may ask us at any time to stop processing your Personal Data, and we will do so, if we are:

  * relying on legitimate interests to process your Personal Data and we cant otherwise demonstrate compelling legal grounds for the processing; or
  * processing your Personal Data for direct marketing.

### Right to withdraw consent

If we rely on your consent as our legal basis for processing your Personal Data, you have the right to withdraw that consent at any time. This will not affect the lawfulness of processing based on your prior consent.

### Right to lodge a complaint with the data protection authority

If you have a concern about any aspect of our privacy practices, including the way we have handled your Personal Data, you can report it to the data protection authority that is authorized to hear those concerns.

## Data Requests

A data subject must be able to:

  * request access to their data to check it for accuracy
  * assess what their data has been used for
  * audit how it has been processed
  * request an electronic copy of their personal data that can be transferred to another organization
  * request that all of their personal data be deleted in a timely manner

You may exercise your rights by contacting us as follows: support@getkisi.com

## Links to Other Websites

Our Website may contain links to other websites that are not under our direct control. These websites may have their own policies regarding privacy. We have no control of or responsibility for linked websites and provide these links solely for the convenience and information of our visitors. You access such linked Websites at your own risk. These websites are not subject to this Privacy Policy. You should check the privacy policies, if any, of those individual websites to see how the operators of those third-party websites will utilize your personal information. In addition, these websites may contain a link to Websites of our affiliates. The websites of our affiliates are not subject to this Privacy Policy, and you should check their individual privacy policies to see how the operators of such websites will utilize your personal information.

## Privacy Policy Updates

We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. You should review this Privacy Policy frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we may notify you on our Website, by a blog post, by email, or by any method we determine. The method we chose is at our sole discretion. We will also change the “Last Updated” date at the beginning of this Privacy Policy. Any changes we make to our Privacy Policy are effective as of this Last Updated date and replace any prior Privacy Policies.

## Questions About Our Privacy Practices or This Privacy Policy

If you have any questions about our Privacy Practices or this Policy, please contact us.
